{
    "subject": "resource/Faiz_Ahmad_Faiz",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Nazm",
    "human_readable": "The genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work Nazm.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9819602966308594,
            "question": "What is the genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work 'Nazm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8496586680412292,
            "question": "How would you describe the style of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's 'Nazm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7087129950523376,
            "question": "Are there any other works by Faiz Ahmad Faiz in a similar genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6410653591156006,
            "question": "What makes 'Nazm' a significant work within its genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5522293448448181,
            "question": "How does 'Nazm' contribute to Faiz Ahmad Faiz's overall literary legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5467751622200012,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other renowned works in the same genre as 'Nazm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46925443410873413,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in 'Nazm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3411131501197815,
            "question": "Is 'Nazm' a poem or a different type of literary work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3334861695766449,
            "question": "To which literary category does 'Nazm' belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2635308504104614,
            "question": "What kind of writing is 'Nazm' characterized by?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work Nazm.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8717_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which literary category does 'Nazm' belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8717_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Nazm' a poem or a different type of literary work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8717_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in 'Nazm'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8717_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8717_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nAccording to the context information, it can be inferred that Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work, including his Nazm poems, embodies a revolutionary aesthetic and critiques oppressive political regimes. Therefore, it can be concluded that the genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work, specifically his Nazm, is indeed related to revolution or social activism.\n\nIn particular, one of the documents mentions that Faiz's poetry \"reverberates with the themes like the issues of the working class, injustice, exploitation of the workers, poverty, and the suffering of ordinary men and women.\" This suggests that his work, including Nazm, has a strong connection to social activism and revolution."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information mentions that Faiz Ahmad Faiz wrote in the style referred to as \u201cnazm,\u201d which aligns with the query about the genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work. Therefore, the triple is correct according to the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}